卡森城 内华达首府
上午 5:02
- 喂?  - 艾米 什么情况?
- Hello? - Okay, what's happening, Amy?
早上好 总统女士 现在是凌晨五点
Morning, Madam President. It's 5:00 A.M.
- 内华达还在睡觉 - 喂? 什么?
- And Nevada is still asleep. - Hello? What?
快他妈起床
Well, wake it the fuck
我在考虑要不要把印第安分区
up 'cause I'm wondering if we should remove
从重新计票的名单里去掉
the Native American precincts from the recount list.
我有点不想保留那个保留地了[Reservation犹豫与印第安居留地两意]
I'm having reservations about the reservations.
赶紧想清楚打给我 我在里德陆军医院
So figure that out and call me right back. I'm at Walter Reed.
接见下军队 还要跟各路妖魔握手
I'm meeting troops and shaking God only knows what.
好的
Okay.
梅耶选票重计办公室
卡森城 内华达
上午 6:43
这是总统最新更改的
These are from the president's last
重新计票区域里的吗?
set of precinct changes for the recount challenge?
是的 还有这之前 以及之前的之前的更改
Yes, and the changes before that and the changes before that.
她改主意的次数比一个
She's changed her mind more
恋童癖到了迪斯尼都多
times than a frickin' child molester at Disneyland.
你需要把这些在17分钟之内上交到法院
You need to file this at the courthouse in exactly 17 minutes.
对 你要是错过了时间期限
Yeah, and if you miss the deadline,
找一条响尾蛇自己爆菊吧
find a rattlesnake and shove that up your dick hole
那样也比我要对你做的事情好得多
'cause it's a lot more fun than what I'll do to you.
一路平安哟
And drive safe.
罗斯福厅 白宫
上午 10:11
哈洛斯 班尼特
We've got Hallowes, Bennett,
还有加比·拉莫斯会在卡森城开发布会
and Gabby Ramos doing press in Carson City
麦多克斯今晚飞过来
and Maddox is flying in tonight.
天呐 麦多克斯估计要用他的鸡巴
Oh, God, Maddox is probably going to study the effects
来领略一下妓女合法化的效果
of legalized prostitution on his dick.
凯瑟琳 出去
Catherine, out.
所以我们知道奥布莱恩
All right, so do we have any idea
这个发布会是关于什么的吗?
what this O'Brien press conference is about?
- 不知道 - 完美
- No idea. - Perfect.
我们正想办法跟艾米视频连线
We're working on our video connection with Amy as we speak.
大概我们该找个六岁的亚洲小孩来修
Well, maybe we can get some six-year-old Asian kid to fix it.
- 迈克 你孩子啥时候来? - 马上啦
- Mike, when's your baby coming? - Coming soon, ma'am.
我们想用温蒂妈妈的名字 叫艾琳
We're gonna name her Ellen after Wendy's mom.
其实是她继母 她跟亲妈关系不太...
Actually, her stepmom. She has a difficult relation...
理解错了 你并不关心 对不起
misunderstood your level of interest, sorry.
各位 在看新闻发布会吗?
Hey, guys, watching the press conference?
废话 艾米 张嘴之前稍微听听
Yeah. Amy, just listen a bit before you start talking.
- 我们的开国元勋... - 好 开始了
- Our founding fathers... - All right, here we go.
...赋予了美国人民选择的权利...
...entrusted the American people with the right to choose...
蒙特兹你们还看得下去?
I mean, will you look at Montez?
我看着都比她西裔
Seriously, I'm more Hispanic than she is.
她哪来的? 康涅狄格州吗?
You know? Where's she from, Santo Connecticut?
Martha's Vineyard 于马萨诸塞 此硬加了西语词缀嘲笑蒙特兹不像西裔
她夏天在马萨葡萄园岛度假
She summers in Vinyardo Del Martha.
蒙特兹还能更不西裔一点吗?
Can Montez look less Hispanic?
天呐艾米 我们已经说过这个了好吗?
Jesus, Amy, we already covered that, okay?
她来自El 新罕布什尔州 [El为西语名词前缀]
She's from El New Hampshire.
...詹姆斯·惠特曼来领导我们的票数重计队伍
...James Whitman to head up our recount team.
- 天哪! 他们居然找了詹姆斯·惠特曼. - 这不是很理想啊
- Jesus! They got James Whitman. - This is not optimal.
我来的地方 一票就是一票 法律就是法律
Where I'm from a vote is a vote, the law is the law,
惠特曼领导内华达重计
- 计票就是计票  - 真有道理啊
- and the count is the count. - He makes a lot of sense.
所以他们找了个州务卿
All right, so they've got
我有什么呢?
a Secretary of State and what do I have?
哈珀 奇科 还有 搅屎托[指喜剧演员组合马克思兄弟]
Harpo, Chico, and Shito.
- 你知道我们需要谁吗? - 谁? 我们需要谁?
- You know who we need? - Who? Who do we need?
鲍勃·布拉德利 我之前的导师
Bob Bradley, my old mentor.
- 雄鹰兄弟会成员 - 太好了
- The Eagle. - That'd be amazing.
比任何活人在政府都待得久
Served in more administrations than any man alive.
还是位相当出色的社交舞舞蹈家
Also an accomplished ballroom dancer.
太好了 就找他了 鲍勃·布拉德利
Okay, great, done. Let's get him. Bob Bradley.
- 他就是我们对付惠特曼的利器 - 总统女士 打扰一下
- He's our Whitman hit man. - Madam President, excuse me.
我和内华达州务卿有个会议
I have the meeting with the Nevada Secretary of State.
艾米 别忘了带上理查德一起
Oh, Amy, don't forget to bring Richard with you.
等一下 真的么 理查德? 他那么…
Wait, really? Richard? He's...
女士 国防部通知我们中国黑客已经
Ma'am, the DOD wants us to know that now the Chinese hackers
盗得我们的白宫工作人员名单
have breached White House employee files.
或许他们能知道这里有些人到底是干嘛吃的
Maybe they can find out what some of these people are doing.
真的是
Ooh, tell me about it.
你要在个早午餐处露个脸
Oh, and you have a drop-by at a brunch
感谢竞选的志愿者们
to thank campaign volunteers.
感谢他们什么?
To thank them for what?
给我创造这奥林匹克比赛游泳池
This Olympic-size swimming pool of shit
一样大的一池子屎 让我可以在里面仰泳?
that I'm doing the backstroke in right now?
这个不建议取消 女士
Not a good idea to cancel, ma'am.
让汤姆做这个
Make Tom do it.
他最喜欢这种假模假样的东西
He loves all that fake smiley shit.
汤姆和他的金融特遣小组在一起
Tom has his banking task force today.
- 他的什么? - 是华尔街的真实版谁是谁
- His what? - It's a veritable who's who of Wall Street.
好吧 听起来比我的事情性感多了
Well, that sounds a lot sexier than my thing.
告诉汤姆我要做这个
Tell Tom that I get dibs on that.
现在是我的总统金融特遣小组了
It's my presidential banking task force now.
汤姆不会高兴的
Well, Tom is not gonna be happy about that.
最好了 我就要这样 开门
Well, good. That's the way I like it. Open the door.
总统马上就要过去握手
The president will be there shaking hands
以及感谢志愿者们的辛劳工作了
and thanking some of the volunteers for their hard work
在不远的将来的某些时刻
at some point in the near future.
再联系
I'll get back.
- 某人今天不吃早餐啦 - 说让你吃了?
- No breakfast for this guy. - Who's offering?
你正在看着一个清肠禁食的人 我感觉棒呆
You are looking at a guy on the master cleanse. I feel amazing.
清肠禁食是什么玩意?
What in the lunatic fuck is the master cleanse?
听起来就像纳粹的内部政策
Sounds like Nazi domestic policy.
关于纳粹的一点小知识
Little known fact about the Nazis
他们在德国内部的投票数 高的吓人
their polling numbers within Germany, through the roof.
不可置信的数字 当然也挺悲剧
Unbelievable numbers. Though also tragic.
犹太民主党就不可能那么强了
The Jewish demo couldn't have been that good.
对 我都不吃东西了
Yep, I don't eat food anymore.
就喝点水 枫糖浆
Just water, maple syrup,
柠檬汁 再来点辣椒粉
lemon juice, and cayenne pepper.
你还拉得出屎?
Do you still take shits?
不能叫拉屎了...
Not exactly take.
内华达州务院
上午 7:33
欢迎来到内华达州
Welcome to Nevada.
大家请坐好 请随意
Everybody settle in. Make yourselves comfortable.
各位梅耶-詹姆斯以及奥布莱恩-蒙特兹团队的成员
Members of the Meyer-James and O'Brien-Montez campaign.
我们先说清规则 根据内华达州法律
Let's talk ground rules. According to Nevada law,
如果重新计票样本结果出现了1%或以上的不一致
if the recount sample shows a difference of 1% or more,
也就是这次的512票
which in this case comes to 512 votes,
我们将要对整个州的投票进行重新计数
we go ahead and recount the whole state.
目前 大部分都是远程在线投票
Now, most of the voting here is touch screen,
所以我们要做到也仅仅是整理所有的投票结果
so we can't do more than retabulate those totals.
但是你能重数选民认证的书面审计索引
Except you could recount the voter-verified paper audit trails.
有时这两者之间可是相差甚远啊
Sometimes there are big discrepancies.
- 先生 这样的话我们想... - 但是
- Sir, in that case we motion... - On the other hand,
第九巡回上诉法庭若引鉴83年克劳利对内华达的判决
the ninth circuit court of appeals ruled in Crowley v. Nevada
这样就不用重新计数
that you don't have to recount
当地的书面审计索引了
the paper audit trails in local elections.
- 是克拉利对内华达? - 是克劳利
- That's Crawley versus Nevada? - That's Crowley.
其实我可以邮件发给你
Actually, you know what? I could email you.
或者你发邮件给我也行 我邮箱是splett2@splettnet.Net.
Or you could email me at splett2@splettnet.Net.
Splett1被我爸用了 虽然他去世我会很难过
Splett1 is my father. It'll be sad to see him go,
但如果能把那个地址归我也蛮好的 你觉得呢
but it'll be nice to get my hands on that handle, you know?
梅耶尔是不是输不起啊?
Is Meyer being a sore loser?
- 总统现在斗志十足 - 总统已经赢了多数票
- Spirits are very high. - The president won the popular vote.
我并没有听到你们所有的问题
I didn't quite catch all your questions.
- 我们在里面碰了个大钉子 - 我们得走了
- We had a pretty big setback in there. - We have to go.
下面的会议我们已经迟到了
We're very late for another appointment.
谢谢大家 非常感谢
Thank you very much, everybody.
你脑子进水了么 你这个帕丁顿熊玩意儿?
What is wrong with you, you Paddington Bear-looking fuck?
你刚刚那简直是给他们了一本时代生活指导手册
You just gave them a Time
专门教他们怎么搞死我们
Life instrction manual on how to fuck us.
你们本来有迈克尔·乔丹在这儿随时恭候
You guys have Michael Jordan sitting on the bench here,
可是非去捧哈基姆·奥拉朱旺
but you're starting Hakeem Olajutwat.
你才不是什么迈克尔·乔丹
You are not Michael Jordan.
你就是个得了马凡式综合征还要死不死的
You are a seven-foot-seven goony-looking Lithuanian
傻大个儿呆逼酒鬼
who's gonna drop dead of Marfan syndrome.
快他妈给我滚上车
Get your ass in the car.
- 雄鹰到来了[引用76年《猛鹰雄风》电影名] - 是的他来了
- The Eagle's landed. -  Yes, he has.
- 总统女士 - 您说?
- Madam President. - Yes?
为您服务我深感荣幸
This is truly an honor to serve you.
好的 真是非常感谢
Well, thank you very much.
况且我绝不会错过
Plus I would never miss the opportunity
花式爆詹姆斯·惠特曼菊花的机会
to dry fuck Jim Whitman up the ass.
凯瑟琳 出去
Catherine, out.
鲍勃我得给你介绍下艾米·布鲁克海默
Oh, Bob, I need to introduce you to Amy Brookheimer
她的团队目前就在内华达
and her team in Nevada right here.
很高兴见到你 布拉德利先生
Nice to meet you, Mr. Bradley.
在卡森市你手上有多少个律师?
How many lawyers you got on the ground in Carson City?
- 我想大概...
- I believe it's roughly...
明天之前把那个数量翻一倍
I want you to double it by the end of the day.
现在 我们来说说重新计票这事
Now, let's talk about the actual recount.
我发现件关于邮寄选票的有意思的事儿
Well, I noticed something funny about the mail-in ballots.
好的 说来听听 平权杰克森[美国一重金属乐队]
All right, let's hear it, Affirmative Action Jackson.
奈县的书记官
Well, the county clerk of Nye
因为签名和选民名单不符
County disqualified a huge number of mail-in ballots
把大量邮件投票计为无效
because the signatures didn't match the voter rolls,
我去查了 发现他是奥布莱恩那派的筹款人
so I checked and he's an O'Brien fundraiser.
他肯定这样作废了大量支持梅耶的选票
He probably chucked out a ton of Meyer votes.
你怎么没去调查这事 金发妞
Why aren't you moving on this, blondie?
对啊 艾米 长点脑子 我的老天
Right, Amy. Come on, get it together. My God in heaven.
我们立刻就去 总统女士 先生
We will get right on it, ma'am, sir.
鲍勃 你怎么看? 你觉得我们能胜出吗?
Bob, what do you think? Are we gonna win this thing?
我是说 你真实的想法
I mean, really honestly, your true gut.
总统女士 我可有很大的信心(巨大的蛋)
Well, Madam President, I've got big balls,
- 而且保证绝对不是虚的 - 真讨厌
- but neither one of them are crystal. - Oh, darn it.
这让我想起尼克松那个屌人在
This reminds me of something that Dick Nixon used to say
打算把美国拉出越南那个泥潭的时候
to Henry Kissinger back when that tricky son of a bitch
冲亨利·基辛格说的话了
was trying to get us out of that messy business called Vietnam.
- 是的 越南 - 他会说 "亨利 你个小婊砸
- Vietnam, right. - He would say, "Henry, you son of a bitch.
师傅领进门之类的我能办到 喂奶我可管不了啊."
I can lead a horse to water, but I can't milk it."
不会喂奶! 我都不知道你在说什么
Can't milk it! I don't even know what that means.
- 但我喜欢 - 我还有一堆电话要打
- I love it. - I've got to make a million phone calls.
- 请允许我失陪一下了 - 没问题
- So you'll have to excuse me. - All right.
- 大家再见 - 再见 太棒了 就是他了
- Good-bye, everyone. - Good-bye. Fantastic. We got our guy.
- 嗨 鲍勃 - 嗯?
- Hey, Bob. - Yeah?
你肯定不记得我了 我是当初那个实习生 在你还是...
You don't remember me. I was an intern way back when you were...
我当然记得你
Of course I remember you.
快瞅瞅 本·卡弗蒂长大了
Lookie here. Ben Cafferty all grown up.
我们原来给这小伙子起了无数个绰号
We used to have a million nicknames for this guy.
我们叫他舔屌胖仔
We called him Fatty Dicksuckle
还有什么笨尼 精爷
and B-B-Benny and the Jizz.
操后门的
Buttfucker.
操后门的 对就是我
Buttfucker, that's me.
不敢相信你都记得我的绰号
I can't believe you remembered my nickname.
看到你太高兴了 非常开心
Good to see you. Nice to see you.
亲爱的老苏 你还在这呢
Oh, good old Sue. You're still here.
- 天啊 天啊 - 还在这?
- My, oh, my. - Still here?
上世纪80年代后他就不在白宫工作了
He hasn't worked in the White House since the late '80s.
苏到底多大啊?
How old is Sue?
内华达选举委员会
需512票可全州重新计数
那一票肯定是投给梅耶的
Well, that's clearly a vote for Meyer.
这写着她名字呢 这是个补名选票
It says her name right there. It's a write-in.
上面写的是 “操赛琳娜·梅耶 "
It says "Fuck Selina Meyer."
怎么说这票该算是我们的
If anything, that one should count for us.
这个算无效
Move to call this a no vote.
别 看到了吗
No, no, no. See, right there.
这有个逗号
See that? Yeah, that's a comma.
- 哪里? - 在 "操" 后面有个逗号
- Where? - After fuck, that is a comma.
所以它意思不是 "操赛琳娜·梅耶尔"
So it doesn't say "Fuck Selina Meyer."
应该是 "操! 赛琳娜·梅耶尔!"
It says, you know, "Fuck, Selina Meyer!"
这正是这个选民对梅耶总统
That's a testament to this voter's earthy
质朴却日月可鉴的热情和支持的证明啊
but unambiguous enthusiasm for President Meyer.
绝对是的
Absolutely.
- 那这票算梅耶 - 好! 太棒了!
- Vote for Meyer. - Yes! Yeah.
- 总统女士 - 你好 经济专家先生
- Madam President. - Yes, Mr. Economy Czar.
银行特派小组会议
上午 11:06
欢迎来到您的金融特遣小组
Welcome to your banking task force.
- 都是您的奇思妙想 - 是吧 我也觉得
- Great idea of yours. - Yeah, it is, isn't it?
我正期待着
I'm looking forward to
什么时候能听见我第二个奇思妙想呢?
hearing what my next great idea is gonna be.
我很高兴看到您把我的政策会谈
Oh, I'm glad that you're able to turn
变成一场毫无意义的拍照秀
my actual policy meeting into a meaningless photo op.
就咱们说话这会儿 我敢肯定道琼斯指数正直冲云霄
I'm sure the Dow is rocketing skywards as we speak.
你不用去个什么志愿者早午餐之类的吗?
Don't you have a volunteers brunch or something to get to?
- 我觉得你要过去啊 - 是啊
- I think you do. - Hmm, yeah.
而且我告诉过你
And I have to tell you,
看那些人吃饭真得很让人享受
it is a pleasure to watch those people eat.
- 失陪了 总统女士 - 放松点
- Madam President. - Yeah, take it easy.
- 哎呀我天 我知道 - 哎呀我天
- Wow. I know. - Wow.
鞋子挺牛逼啊 老板
Boss boots, boss.
谢谢 纯鳄鱼皮的
Oh, thanks. Yeah, check those out. Genuine crocodile skin.
对啊 我穿上这玩意儿放倒克林特·伊斯特伍德
Yeah, I'm gonna be pulling down Clint Eastwood
那些牛仔电影里的娘娘腔都不成问题
cowboy movie style pussy in these things.
只不过我不是无名之人
Except I'm not the man with no name.
我是个各路吊炸天之人
I'm the man with mo' game.
下午好先生 您的投票被取消了
Afternoon, sir. We're here because your ballot
因为您的签名不符合...
was disqualified because your signature didn't match...
好吧 把我当傻子耍了
okay, well, fooled me with that one.
- 咱们团队合作的不错 - 干得漂亮 理查德
- Good job, team. - Yeah, nice job, Richard.
如果我是领导的话肯定不会这么做
That's not how I would've done it if I was in charge.
那你怎么做
How would you have done it?
我不能教你怎么做
I can't teach how I do it.
你说保罗·麦卡特尼能教会摇滚小子怎么写歌吗
Can Paul McCartney teach Kid Rock how to be a good songwriter?
当然 这个例子不恰当 摇滚小子最强 但是...
I mean, that's a bad example. Kid Rock rules, but...
女士 这是查理·贝尔德 韦瑞特公司首席执行官
Hey, ma'am, this is Charlie Baird, CEO of EM Wheelright.
- 您好 总统女士 - 你就是查理·贝尔德啊
- Hello, Madam President. - You're Charlie Baird.
- 对 很高兴见到您 - 高兴见到你
- I am. Good to see you. - Yes, good to see you, too.
- 感谢你的光临 - 我的荣幸
- Thanks for coming today. - My pleasure.
我以为会花上两个小时
I thought this was going to be two hours
来听汤姆·詹姆斯提醒我们收入太高了
of Tom James lecturing us about being paid too much.
汤姆有时是 要是我能说...
Well, Tom can be, dare I say...
有点傻逼?
A bit of an asshat?
其实我是想说 他是中产阶级的代表
Actually, I was gonna say a champion for the middle class,
但是诚实点 我好像更喜欢你的说法
but I kind of like your thing better to tell you the truth.
女士 这位是菲利普·瑞安 他是
Ma'am, this is Phillip Ryan. He's the
- 你能先等一下嘛  - 当然
- Can you hang on just two seconds? - Of course.
问你个事
So let me ask you this.
市场到底出了什么问题
What in the heck is going on with the markets?
- 不知道 - 好吧
- I don't know. - Oh, great.
我只知道昨天早上
I do know that yesterday morning
这个房间比现在聪明250亿美元
this room felt about $25 billion smarter.
我猜那是你们
Yeah, I think that's what
捐给我对手的钱 对吧
all of you donated to my opponent, right?
坦白地说 我也为你的选举捐钱了
Full disclosure, I did donate to your campaign as well.
两千吗
Two grand?
你从哪找到这笔钱的 你的沙发缝里
Where'd you find that? In your sofa seat cushion?
好像在我另外一条裤子口袋里 总统女士
I think it was in my other pants, Madam President.
- 很好 欢迎你的到来  - 女士
- Good. Nice to have you here. - Hey, ma'am.
- 这位是伊莱·帕克 CM资本的首席执行官  - 是吗
- This is Eli Park. He's the CEO of CM Capital. - Oh, yes.
- 伊莱你好啊 - 总统女士
- Oh, hello, Eli. - Madam President.
- 苏珊还好吗  - 他离婚了
- Yes, how is Susan? - He's divorced.
她这么对你 都没进监狱
Not in jail for what she did to you.
真的太过分了 但是很高兴在这里见到你
Honestly, it is an outrage. But I'm happy you're here.
我们要开始这个会议了 对吧
And I think we've got to get this meeting going, don't we?
- 是的 - 对 对
- It's got to get - yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 谢谢你  - 谢谢您 总统女士
- Thank you. - Thank you, Madam President.
非常感谢 哎呀我的妈
Oh, thank you very much. Oh, Jesus Christ.
不用担心伊莱
Don't worry about Eli.
布克兄弟做西装的时候是把婚前协议一起绣给我们的
Brooks Brothers sews prenups into all our suits.
- 你也离婚了 - 对啊 我骄傲
- Oh, are you divorced? - Oh, yeah, proudly.
我和我丈夫做的最正确的一件事
Yeah, best thing me and my husband ever did.
包括我女儿在内
Including our daughter.
听着 我听说你在彭博新闻上
Listen, I heard you on Bloomberg
大谈特谈我的经济头脑
talking about my financial acumen,
我只能说你太过分了
and I have to say you were wildly out of line.
我说的话大多数是为了节目效果
Well, most of that is just for show.
但是 出于对您的尊重 总统女士
But, with all due respect, Madam President,
您的一些经济政策
some of your economic policies
用我朋友凯蒂·格罗斯的话说 是一堆狗屎
are what my friend Katie Gross likes to call fakakta.
凯蒂·格罗斯 你认识她?
Katie Gross? You know Katie Gross?
我跟凯蒂·格罗斯的一起去的史密斯学院
I went to Smith with Katie Gross.
- 我跟凯蒂·格罗斯约会过 - 我也是
- I dated Katie Gross. - Yeah, so did I.
因为我上的是史密斯啊 不好意思这是个学校内部梗
'Cause I was at Smith. No, it's a Smith joke.
- 简直不可思议 - 这位是伊丽莎白·穆尔豪斯
- That's incredible. - This is Elizabeth Moorehouse.
- 你好吗 - 很好 谢谢
- Oh, hi, how are you? - I'm well, thank you.
- 感谢光临  - 我的荣幸 总统女士
- Thank you for coming today. - My pleasure, Madam President.
我希望您能劝劝联邦储备局
I hope you can talk some sense into the fed.
对不起 打断一下
Excuse me, sorry to interrupt.
总统女士 凯蒂让我告诉您Hubbard万岁
Madam President, Katie says to tell you Hubbard forever.
- 不会吧  - 是的
- She didn't. - She did.
她不是吧 太搞笑了
She didn't! That's hilar--
那是我们的宿舍 超恶心的
that was our dorm and it was repulsive.
- 你认识凯蒂·格罗斯吗  - 有点耳熟
- You know Katie Gross? - It sounds familiar.
你肯定跟她见过
I bet your paths have crossed.
第二个签名是卡尔中风的时候签的
The second signature was when Carl had his stroke.
太棒了 我是说对我们来说很好
Oh, that's fantastic. I mean, fantastic for us
因为这意味着他投给梅耶总统的票是合法的
because it means that his vote for President Meyer is legitimate.
- 他可以作证吗  - 抱歉 他已经过世了
- Could he testify to that? - I'm sorry, he's passed.
节哀 你应该读读C.S.刘易斯关于悲痛的书
Sorry. You should read C.S. Lewis's book on grief.
倒是没有《狮子 巫师和壁橱》系列那么好玩
It's not as fun as "The Lion, Witch, and the Wardrobe" Series,
- 但还是一本不错的书  - 女士 您好
- but it's still pretty good. - Ma'am, hi.
乔纳·瑞安 梅耶选举团队
Jonah Ryan, Senior Deputy
高级重新计票副战略师
Recount Strategist for the Meyer campaign.
我们可以进去等您丈夫吗
Would it be all right if we waited for your husband inside?
- 我好想长了个水疱  - 抱歉啊
- I think I have a small blister. - I'm sorry.
愿安息 是希伯来语
Alav hashalom. Hebrew.
你是不是应该穿双正常的鞋子
Maybe you should put on your regular shoes for a little bit?
告诉你 我受够了你那个狗屁的微观管理
You know what? I am sick of your micromanaging bullshit.
但是如果你坚持的话 我可以去宾馆停一下
But if you insist, yes, I will stop by the hotel.
可以啊 走两分钟
We can do that. It's a two-minute walk.
不对 是两英里[约3.218km]
Oh, sorry, two miles.
老天爷
God.
内华达选举委员会
需185票可全州重新计数
快来看看 这既然不是巨星艾伦·德杰尼勒斯[艾伦秀]
Well, well, well, if it isn't TV's Ellen DeGeneres
那一定是艾米·布鲁克海默了
and of course Amy Brookheimer.
弗朗议员
Congressman Furlong, to what do we owe
什么阴风把您给吹来了
this pleasure slash skin-crawling sensation?
我刚到西部跟这个傻大个子Cosplay了一下
Well, I just came out West to play a little Cowboys and Injuns
牛仔和印第安人
with Big Chief Suckum Choad here.
说吧
Say it.
嚎
How.
我在帐篷里吃鸡鸡
Me suck pee pee in teepee.
好姑娘
Atta girl.
实际上 鲍勃·布拉德利让我来这里
Actually, Bob Bradley asked me to come out here
用我这颗政治明星的光芒
and dazzle some of these
闪瞎这些山炮的双眼
armadillo fuckers with my political star power.
让开 你们这些横在路上的尸体 大咖来了
Step aside, roadkill. Big rig coming through.
嗨 艾米 丹
Hi, Amy, Dan.
- 嘿  - 都好不
- Hi again. - How you doing?
这不算重复投票吧
That is not an overvote.
投票人划掉了奥布莱恩的名字 投给了梅耶
The voter crossed out O'Brien's name and voted for Meyer.
这是给梅耶的一票啊
That is a vote for Meyer.
这个算重复投票
Move to rule it an overvote.
嘿 奶昔大哥[巨大紫色长毛麦当劳吉祥物] 你他妈...
Hey, Grimace. What are you...
不 没说你
no, no, no, not you.
我是说这个房间里另外一个长得跟奶昔大哥一毛一样的家伙
The other person in the room who looks exactly like Grimace.
这不是重复票了 你得相信我
That is not an overvote. You need to trust me on this
因为在你妈从试图从楼梯上滚下来之前
because I've been doing this since before your mother
我就已经开始干这个活了
was throwing herself down the stairs belly first.
你要我帮你拿副眼镜来么?
You want me to get you some glasses?
或者我可以把奶酪市长找来?[同为麦当劳人偶]
Maybe I'll call in Mayor McCheese?
他可以进来跟你解释一下这个选举的过程
He can come in here and explain election procedures to you.
我没想
Oh, I'm not...
- 特蕾西 - 看 是因为你穿了紫色
- Tracy. - Look, it’s... you're wearing purple.
跟你的身材没什么关系
All right? It's got nothing to do with your body shape
也不是因为你的脑袋跟肩膀无缝衔接
or your the way your head goes into your shoulders so smoothly.
我们差不多得去下一场会议了
Hey, you know, we have to get to your next meeting at the
对 说得好 上帝保佑你
That's right. Good call. God bless you.
上帝保佑美国
God bless America.
当你心情平复了之后
When you're ready,
我们想要严正质疑一下你的决定
we would like to vigorously contest your ruling.
女士 我有一些金融特遣小组的照片需要批准
Oh, ma'am, I have photos to approve from the banking task force.
然后您在五分钟之后要跟奥林匹克获奖者见面
And you have a meeting with Olympic medalists in five.
残疾的还是正常的?
Special or normal?
他们看起来挺正常 不过我会确认一下
they seemed normal, but I'll confirm.
好的
Okay.
你昨晚在电视上看《教父》了嘛?
So you catch "The Godfather" On TV last night?
- 没有 - 没有什么能比得上
- No. - There was nothing like seeing it in the theater
1972年在电影院里看这部电影了
when it first came out back in '72.
我不关心电影
I don't care for movies.
你的划船事业实在是为我们美国争了光
You've truly brought honor to America with your kayaking.
恭喜你获得金牌
So congratulations on your gold medal.
- 铜牌 - 噢是铜牌
- It's bronze. - Oh. Oh, bronze medal.
拍到了吗? 谢谢你送给我这个
Did we get it? Oh, and thank you for this.
我等不及要去波托马克河试一把了
I can't wait to try it out on the Potomac.
- 好了 往这边走 - 好的
- All right, guys. Right this way. - Okay.
好样的
Great. Great. Great. Great. Okay.
我他妈能拿这玩意干毛使?
Fuck am I supposed to do with this?
- 放你图书馆估计会不错 - 啥?
- It'd be nice for your library. - What?
凯瑟琳 出去
Catherine, out.
所以媒体怎么说我们的金融特遣组?
So what's the press saying about our banking task force?
他们喜欢得合不拢腿
They opened wide and slurped it down, ma'am.
你知道我在想什么吗?
You know what I was thinking?
我想啊
I was thinking that I
我想再成立一个金融特遣组
would like to do another banking task force.
我们估计能请来巴克莱银行的帕伦贝格
I bet we could get Pallenberg at Barclays.
很好啊
I see no problem there.
不要 那个懂很多的韦瑞特公司的
No, you know who had a lot to say was that guy from Wheelright.
查理... 贝尔德
Charlie... Baird.
- 你当真? - 是啊
- Really? - Uh-huh.
女士 我觉得现在吧
Ma'am, I don't think right now
不适合成立另一个金融特遣组
would be the best time for another banking task force.
我就想要个简单快速的金融特遣组
No, I just want to have a quick banking task force.
听我一言 女士 您要知道
With all due respect, ma'am, you know, the banks will still be,
金融还是会在那儿 等您的特遣的
you know, raring to go for a task force,
您要等自己成功选上总统之后
you know, when you're safely reelected.
我也是人好吗? 我就是想要...
I'm human, okay? I just...
我就是需要一点点的金融特遣组啊
I just sometimes need a little banking task force.
女士 如果你想要的话
Well, ma'am, if you want,
我可以安排一个低调私密的小组
I can arrange a more discreet banking task force.
我才不要那种金融特遣组
I don't want that kind of banking task force.
我要我看上的金融特遣组
I want the banking task force that I want.
德国银行的帕蒂·得利斯怎么样?
What about Patty Driscoll from Deutsche Bank?
她能力很强 在组里加一个女性也许很有利
She's very good. Might be nice to throw a woman in the mix.
女士 艾米的视频会议
Ma'am, Amy's on video conference.
艾米 怎么了?
Amy, what is it?
- 您能看到我吗? 我看不到你 - 好吧
- Can you see me? I can't see you. - Yeah.
- 我在你的屏幕上吗? - 看不看得到有关系吗?
- Am I on your screen? - Who cares if you can't see me?
我们又不是在找对方的头皮屑
We're not looking at each other's hairdos.
内华达州怎么样了?
What's going on in Nevada?
- 肯特 你屁股下面有个瓶子吗? - 别吵吵
- Kent, are you sitting on a bottle? - Shh, shh!
- 女士 你在哪儿? - 艾米?
- Ma'am, where are you? - Amy?
啊看到了 投票站总数已经出来了
Ah, there you are. Precinct totals have been reported.
我们拿到了... 票
We got... votes.
等下 你掉线了 你刚刚说什么?
Wait, you just went out. What did you just say?
我们拿到了... 票
We got... votes.
- 我们拿到几票? - 我从固话打
- How many votes did we get? - Let me try a landline.
- 我快疯掉了 - 好了好了
- I'm losing my mind. - We got it. We got it.
512票 全州要重新统计票数
512 votes. Full state recount is a go.
重新特么的统计!
Fucking recount!
- 我的妈啊 - 真是个好消息
- Oh, my God! - This is favorable news.
噢上帝啊 我赢定了 我赢定了
Oh, my God, this is my house. This is my house.
嘿 大伙 听着
Hey, guys, listen up. Okay,
投票站票数已经重新算了 而且
precinct totals have been reported and
把她挂了 等下 凯瑟琳呢?
Oh, just hang up on her. Wait, where is Catherine?
她应该把这段拍进她的小电影里
She should be getting this for her little movie.
我头有点晕
I'm feeling light-headed.
那瓶子是我唯一的血糖来源了
That bottle's my only source of blood sugar.
好了 盖瑞 我需要跟查理·贝尔德再见一面
Okay, Gary, I'm wanna get Charlie Baird in for another meeting.
您想要我再邀请别的人吗
You want me to invite some other people?
- 不不不 就他 - 噢
- No, no, no, just him. - Oh.
- 就他吗? - 嗯
- Just him? - Yep.
喏 你的傻瓶子
Here's your stupid bottle.
别演日本歌舞伎了 吃块饼干去吧
Stop with the Kabuki show and eat a fucking cookie.
迈克  跟我讲一下这后面的科学依据
Uh, Mike, remind me again the science behind this.
现在我感觉可棒了
Now I feel great.
你们真的得试试这个
You guys have got to try this.
星期天的脱口秀里面我们需要找人去
We need surrogates for the Sunday talk shows.
- 对哦 - 陈州长说他会去
- Right. - Chung will do it.
为了全国转播
Chung would volunteer for
被砍头的视频他也会报名去的
a beheading video to get national airtime.
我其实还蛮想看的
I'd actually like to see that.
女士 汤姆·詹姆斯来这里见你
Ma'am, Tom James is here sans appointment.
你能去让他操一袋玻璃渣啥的吗?
Bleh. Can you go tell him to fuck a bag of glass or something?
其实 我差不多说了一样的
Actually, I told him something
不过他好像蛮坚持要见你的
similar to that, but he's most insistent.
好吧 带他进来
Oh, okay. Send him in.
嘿 这简直是意外的惊喜
Hi there. This is an unexpected pleasure.
不 大家 我想要你们也听着
No, no, no, guys. I want you to hear this.
女士 对我来说 我完全可以理解
Ma'am, on reflection, I totally understand
为什么你想要带头领导金融特遣组
why you needed to take the lead on the banking task force.
而且我已经全力做好帮助这个小组的准备了
And I am ready to do whatever I need to do to help the team.
所以 不论是经济专家 还是小孩的生日聚会 还是当可怜人
So, economy czar, kids' birthday parties, reflecting pool boy.
只是别让我当联合国大使
Just don't ask me to be the United Nations ambassador
我还是要点脸的
cause I still have some pride.
就不打扰你们了
I wanted to say that and I'll leave you guys alone.
- 非常感谢 - 谢谢 很高兴见到你
- Thank you so much. - Oh, great. Thanks. Good to see you.
对了 我刚把艾森豪威尔行政办公室的地板擦亮了
Oh, by the way, I just polished the floor in the Eisenhower Room.
- 汤姆 少来了 - 在那儿要小心点哦
- Tom, stop. - Be careful in there, all right?
- 这是干啥? - 的确不对劲
- Huh? - That was something.
为什么汤姆·詹姆斯突然把他的蛋蛋打包好
Why did Tom James just wrap up
还主动给我放钱包里啊?
his balls in butcher paper and put them in my purse?
因为他觉得你会拿下内华达州
Because he thinks you're gonna win Nevada.
- 汤姆觉得我会拿下内花达? - 是的
- Tom thinks I'm gonna win Nevada? - Yeah.
- "内华达" - 他才是首都最精明的人呢？
- "Nev-add-a." - He's the smartest guy in DC.
看到没? 他可比你们这些蠢蛋聪明多了
You know that? He's a lot smarter than you dummies.
说真的 要是汤姆认为我会赢的话 我肯定能赢
Seriously, if Tom thinks I'm gonna win Nevada, I'm gonna win.
女士 查理·贝尔德来这儿了
Ma'am, Charlie Baird is here.
嘿 我又会继续当总统了
Hey, I'm gonna be president,
要是我想的话 我都可以在玫瑰园拉屎了
so I can go take a shit in the Rose Garden if I want to.
我们过去称那为吉米·卡特（美国第39任总统）
We used to call that a Jimmy Carter.
查理·贝尔德 让开
Charlie Baird. Move.
总统女士 我好惊喜啊
Madam President. What a lovely surprise.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
我还以为我2000美元的捐款只能让我拍张照呢
I thought my $2,000 donation only entitled me to a photo.
- 你好吗? - 很好 充满活力
- How are you? - I am good. I am energized.
对了 你早些时候说到的关于
So, you know, you made an
债券市场很有意思的点...
interesting point earlier today about the bond market...
要不然这样 谈正事之前
but you know what? Before we do that,
你想先逛逛
would you like to go on
白宫西厢吗?
a tour of the West Wing? Would that be fun?
不确定您有时间做这个
I don't know if you have time for that,
我有
Yeah, I have time.
- 好啊 - 那好
- Okay. - Yeah? Okay.
提醒一下 我五年级班级旅游时
I warn you, I had a pretty comprehensive
已经把白宫里里外外参观过一遍了噢
White House tour on my fifth grade class trip.
实际上我了解不少西厢的历史 要是你感... 不
I actually know a lot about West Wing history if you'd like... no.
我感觉那个人好像不太喜欢我啊
I feel like that guy doesn't like me very much.
- 谁 盖瑞? - 对
- Who, Gary? - Yeah.
不可能 你这样说就像说哪只猫不喜欢你
Come on, that's like saying that the cat doesn't like you
或者说那台桌子不喜欢你一样
or that table doesn't like you.
往前走有幅诺曼·洛克威尔的话
Okay, now, there's this Rockwell down here
太迷人了 我发誓
that is so stunning and
要是选举落败了的话
I swear to God if I lose this fucking election,
我一定要把它放在我的行李箱中带走
I'm gonna stick it in my suitcase and I'm taking it with me.
- 我爱洛克威尔 - 是啊
- Love Rockwell. - Yeah.
- 我有一大堆他的作品 - 你有?
- I have a bunch of Rockwells. - You do?
- 是啊 - 别骗我
- Yeah. - You're kidding.
- 说真的 - 在哪儿呢?
- No. - Where are they?
海滨别墅里
Some beach house.
- 不确定在哪个海边 - 真有你的
- Not sure which beach. - You are wild.
要是别人这样说 我肯定觉得他在吹牛
In another person it would be bragging,
你就不同了
but with you it's something different.
等会儿 我得让你看看这里
Oh, wait a minute. I got to show you this.
看到这个贮藏室了吗?
Okay, see this closet?
不知道你听说过没
I don't know if you've heard about this,
沃伦·哈定就在这儿和他未成年的情妇
but this is the actual closet where Warren Harding
搞了一个孩子出来
fathered a child with his teenage mistress.
我五年级参观时 他们可没讲这个
They left that off our fifth grade tour.
他们带你们参观了居住室吗?
Did they show you the residence?
没呢
Nope.
你想看吗?
Uh, you want to see the residence?
当然
Uh, yeah.
好
Okay.
- 卧槽 今天 - 是投今天一票的意思吗?
- Fuck, today. - Now, was that a vote in favor of today?
就是卧槽 逗号 今天的意思 当然是啦
Oh, that was a fuck, comma, today, yes!
那个... 我住这儿
Oh, I didn't... yeah, this is me.
我住这儿
This is me. Uh...
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Okay, good night. - Good night, yeah.
- 该死 别这样啊
- God damn it. Come on. -
天啊
Jesus Christ.
我又得去换一次钥匙卡了
I've had to get this key card changed twice.
- 因为它... - 让我来
- Because it's like... - Okay, allow me.
- 嗨 艾米 - 哇哦
- Ooh, hi, Amy. - Whoa.
你可没告诉我这个基佬发型男在这儿
You didn't tell me faggy hair was here.
苏菲 几年没见了
Sophie, haven't seen you in years.
你的私生子们过得还好吗?
How are your illegitimate children?
我让我姐给我寄换洗衣服来
I asked my sister to send me a change of clothes
没想到她亲自送来了
and apparently she has decided to bring them herself.
- 这样啊 - 这个旅馆房间糟糕死了
- Uh-huh. - Your hotel room sucks.
我还以为卡森市是拉斯维加斯的一部分呢
I thought that Carson City was, like, part of Las Vegas.
维加斯在432公里之外呢
Vegas is 432 miles away.
不好意思我不是什么"地图全知道"怪咖
Sorry I'm not a "Where everything is" Nerd.
你们俩之前是准备来一炮吗?
Were you two just about to bone?
这
Okay, well,
你慢慢享受吧
you enjoy all that.
- 我得... - 别 别 别啊
- I'm gonna... - Oh, no, no, no.
在拉斯维加斯就要及时行乐啊
What happens in Vegas, it stays in Vegas.
这不是拉斯维加斯
We're not in Vegas.
要知道 我可从没和休斯总统这么干过呢
You know, I hardly ever did that with President Hughes.
就算做
And even when we did,
我也是走走过场
I was just kind of going through the motions.
谢谢你哈 太受宠若惊了
Oh, thank you very much. That's very flattering.
- 也许我们能... - 我们得走了
- Maybe we can do this... - We got to get you out of here.
- 好 - 我要打电话给盖瑞
- Right. - I'm gonna call Gary
让他把你送到东南大门
and get him to take you to the southeast gate.
请让盖瑞接一下电话 谢谢
Can you send Gary up here, please? Yeah, thank you.
- 但我真觉得很高兴 - 别这样 我也是的
- But I really did have a great time. - No, no, no, I did, too.
我的意思是 我不是那种总统
I mean, I'm just saying I'm not that kind of a president.
- 我懂 - 你看见我的鞋了吗?
- Got it. - Yeah. Do you know where my shoes are?
- 好像... 我们在那儿开始的 - 看到了
- I think you... we started in there. - Yes, they're here.
- 进来! - 走吧
- Come in! - Okay, let's go.
你一定是盖瑞吧 我们还没正式打过招呼呢
You must be Gary. We haven't officially met.
我是查理·贝尔德
I'm Charlie Baird.
很高兴见到你
Uh, nice to meet you.
你是哪里人?
Where you from?
- 阿拉巴马州 伯明翰市 - 一个被低估的城市啊
- Birmingham, Alabama. - Ah, underrated city.
我完全同意你
You're telling me.
我早就这样觉得了
人们称它为南方的匹兹堡
They call it the Pittsburgh of the South.
你是来自个大家庭吧?
You come from a big family, do you?
我是来自一个大家庭 是的 是的
I do come from a big family. I do, I do, I do.
实际上家里就我一个孩子
It's actually just me. I'm an only child.
盖瑞 你能送贝尔德先生到东南大门吗?
Oh, Gary, can you take Mr. Baird to the southeast gate, please?
这么快吗?
Oh, so soon?
鲍勃 我想知道的是
But what I want to know, Bob,
我们要在所以的农村选区设个重新计票小组
is do we put a full recount team in all the rural precincts
还是我们只关注里诺和维加斯就行?
or do we just focus on Reno and Vegas?
好吧 你这是典型的
Well, what you have here
两只手着火只有一只手套的情况
is a classic two fires, one glove situation.
你需要知道的是哪个手戴手套
And you need to know which hand to put the glove on.
- 完全正确 - 没错
- That's exactly right. - Exactly.
总统女士
You know, as much as it pains me
我得赶紧走了
to leave your company, Madam President,
我得去赶一班去内布拉斯加的飞机
I got to catch a flight to Nebraska.
不 等一下 你说内华达 内华达
No, oh, wait a minute. You mean Nevada. Nevada.
- 我说什么了? - 你说内布拉斯加
- What did I say? - You said Nebraska.
- 我也替你把内布拉斯加拿下吧 - 好的
- Well, I'll get that one for you, too. - Okay.
我的好友啊 一路顺风
Listen, safe travels, my friend.
谢谢 先生们
Thank you. Gentlemen.
- 操后门的 - 拜拜 鲍勃
- Buttfucker. - Bye, Bob.
- 现在都产不出他那样的了 - 最好的版本了
- Honestly, they don't make them like that anymore. - The best.
- 他来自一个不同的年代啊 - 伟人时代再降临的感觉
- He's from a different age. - When giants walked these halls.
- 女士 - 嗯?
- Ma'am. - Yeah?
30分钟后你要和加拿大贸易代表团会面
You have a drop-by with the Canadian Trade Delegation in 30.
- 我都忘了这事儿了 - 还有 查理·贝尔德上电视了
- Oh, I forgot about that. - And FYI, Charlie Baird's on TV.
你知道 我在东楼看到一幅
You know, I was over in the East Wing and I saw a painting of Sue
苏握着华盛顿的马的画
holding George Washington's horse.
参议员比尔奥布莱恩发言说...
Senator Bill O'Brien made remarks...
凯瑟琳 我都不知道怎么说了 出去
Catherine, I can't even begin. Out.
查理·贝尔德是我一个朋友
Charlie Baird is a friend of mine.
查理·贝尔德是这个时代最伟大的金融家之一
Charlie Baird is one of the great financial minds of our time
对任何政府都是重要的人才
and would be an asset to any administration.
- 你在逗我 - 不
- You're kidding. - No.
他操了我 然后又这样操翻了我?
He fucked me and then he fucked me?
怎么回事 他准备操死我吗?
What, is he trying to fuck me?
他一定特别抱歉
I bet he's really sorry.
白宫
下午 9:16
嘿 女士 查理来了
Hey, ma'am, Charlie's here.
他看起来挺伤心的
He seems really sad.
- 我生气时总是数到十再... - 闭嘴
- I always count to 10... - Shut it.
你从这直接跑去奥布莱恩的酒店去了?
You went straight from here to O'Brien's hotel?
你在逗我? 你这之间最起码起了个澡没有啊?
Are you kidding me? Did you take a shower at least in between?
这只是一个关于他的内阁的初步会议
It was just a preliminary meeting regarding his cabinet.
你操我的时候也在想他的内阁吗?
Were you thinking about his cabinet while you were fucking me?
说正经的 你是不是还在幻想我有着山羊胡子
Seriously. Were you fantasizing I had some sort of a goatee
并且还在肝移植等候名单上?
and was on the wait list for a liver?
与奥布莱恩的会面在我们见面之前就早已经计划好了
The O'Brien meeting was scheduled days before we even met.
我不认为这里面有利益冲突
I didn't think it was a conflict of interests.
你不认为这是冲突
You didn't think it was a conflict
首先 他都没有内阁
first of all, he doesn't even have a cabinet.
你看 即使你赢了大选 也没什么意义
Look, if you win the election, it doesn't mean anything anyway.
- 但如果奥布莱恩赢了大选 - 好 我们来听听
- If O'Brien wins the election - Okay, let's hear what this is.
你就和财政部长睡过了
you've slept with the Secretary of the Treasury.
噢真好啊 我们算完了
Oh, that's classy. This is over.
完了? 我也没拿它当事儿啊
Over? I didn't even know it was a thing.
当然不是事儿啊 并且即使这是件事儿 也已经过去了
Absolutely not a thing. And if it was a thing, it's over.
是的
Yeah.
- 怎么样啦? - 他们在等你了
- How we doing? - They're ready for you.
那我们就放手做吧
Then let's get 'er done!
我杯子去哪儿了 我杯子呢?
Oh, where's my bottle? My bottle?
是这个吗
Is this it?
谢谢 我需要它保持住血糖
Thanks. Got to keep the old blood sugar up.
各位 晚上好
Good evening, everyone.
提问之前先告诉你们 内华达没有任何进展
Before you ask, there are no updates on Nevada.
总统专注于经济
The president is laser-focused on the economy,
所以我很愿意谈谈这个
so I'd be happy to address that.
- 迈克 迈克 - 黛比
- Mike, Mike! - Deb.
可以说相应的刺激计划正在出台吗?
Can we expect a stimulus package?
是的 现在各种措施都在被考虑
Yes, right now all options are on the table.
包括经济刺激计划
Uh, including a stimulus package,
也在被考虑
uh, which is on the table.
- 迈克! - 韦恩
- Mike! - Wayne.
总统为什么今天接见了查理·贝尔德
Why did the president bring Charlie Baird in again today
尤其在他和奥布莱恩方面见面之后?
after he met with the O'Brien camp?
查理·贝尔德...
Uh, Charlie Baird, uh...
他就是 过来开个会
he's just-- came in for a meeting.
就开个会 他是顾问
Just a meeting. He's an advisor.
事实上不仅是顾问
Uh, actually not an advisor.
他是查理·贝尔德
Uh, he-- he's a Charlie Baird.
迈克 梅耶总统和查理贝尔德
Mike, what exactly is the nature of President Meyer's
到底是什么关系?
relationship with Charlie Baird?
提问结束 我得走了
No more questions. I do have to go.
看起来像是查理贝尔德和总统在上床啊
Looks like Charlie Baird is fucking the president.
卡森城 内华达
下午 11:00
我给我妹单独订了个房间
You know, I got my sister her own room.
所以就是小小的你
So it's just little old you
在大大的房房里
in that big old room.
我要回房去了
I'm gonna go back to that room.
回见
See you later.
哈喽
Well, hello.
这的人都好无聊
Everybody here is so boring.
你们每天干的活都是狗屎
The shit you do is such bullshit.
提醒我一下你每天在做什么有趣的事呢?
Remind me again what it is that you do that's so interesting.
我在CVS工作[CVS药房类似屈臣氏]
I work at CVS.
真的?CBS?[CBS为美哥伦比亚广播公司缩写]
Really? CBS?
我超想去CBS上班诶
I would love to work at CBS.
- 天你别混蛋行不行 - 我认真的
- Oh, God, don't be a dick. - No, I'm serious.
反正永远在找人啊
There's always openings.
你觉得你能帮我介绍到工作吗?
Do you seriously think that you could get me something?
- 也许深夜的 - 深夜很好啊
- Maybe late night. - Late night's perfect!
你想离开这吗
Do you want to get out of here?
我有自己的房间的
I have my own room.
是的
Uh, yeah.
- 棒 走吧 - 好的
- Cool, let's go. - Yeah.
- 走吧 - 好的
- Let's go! - Yeah.
这是我的号码 直接接到我这的
And this is my number and it goes straight to me.
你可以随时打电话给我 我一直在
You can call me any time of the day. I'm always here.
- 谢谢你 伯明翰小子 - 好的
- Thank you, Birmingham. - Okay.
贝尔德先生 你确认你在和梅耶总统交往吗?
Mr. Baird! Can you confirm that you are dating President Meyer?
你和总统第一次见面是什么时候?
When did you and the president first meet?
贝尔德先生 你在和总统约会吗?
Mr. Baird, are you dating the president?
祝各位晚安
Have a lovely night.
约一杯吗
约吗
你在哪
算了我睡了
约一杯
华盛顿特区
上午 5:43
23条短信?
23 messages?
约一杯?
A nightcap?
"我在特区"
"I'm in DC."